(A few weeks ago)
Brother Kin, we have been following
that rich lady.
She jogs near her villa every night
at around 10 o'clock.
That's too early.
Clear Water Bay is a rich neighborhood.
Nobody is out and about after 8 o'clock.
That woman lives near the hillside
where there's no CCTV and quite dark
with few street lamps.
We can ambush her right there.
The client is paying USD$500K
and wants her dead.
That's easy...I'll grab her by the neck
from behind
and stab her a dozen times.
That should kill her.
Or we bring a chainsaw
and cut her up right here...
Dummy can make a video.
I'll tell the client
once the Boss gets paid,
we'll take action.
Wait for my order.
Good!
Morning, gentlemen!
Sorry, Brother Kin! I overslept again.
You're in a meeting?
Let me record this...
What are you talking about?
A hit.
What recording? Are you nuts?
You told me I'm the secretary,
I came down without putting makeup on.
Don't get on my case.
Brother Kin is not scolding you.
You're so pretty even without makeup...
You skin is so fair...
Your skin is smooth as tofu...
Cut the crap!
They're probably hungry.
Let's order afternoon tea.
Are you on the menu?
Hey...
Do they have rice noodles?
Do it over there.
We still have business to discuss.
Rice noodles?
What's the story with the bank?
We've been doing site survey
for a few days.
Cops don't go out there during the day.
We can take action any time.
I have the tools ready.
I mapped out the getaway route.
OK, let's do it tomorrow.
Stay on your toes
and get me a few hundred thousand.
We have a pretty suitcase.
Miss, planning a trip lately?
Just fill out this form for the suitcase.
Miss, have you heard of a virtual bank?
A virtual bank is also a bank.
A virtual credit card is still
a credit card.
The upside is you don't need a physical card
so you won't need to worry about it
being stolen.
When you apply for the card,
we'll give a pretty suitcase.
Sign your pretty name here
and you'll get the pretty suitcase.
It's OK...
Thanks!
Just fill this out...
Miss, you wish to apply for
this virtual credit card?
If I apply for it, I'll get this suitcase?
Yes, but while stocks last.
I want to apply.
Please come this way. Your ID card please?
A photocopy? Is that OK?
Should be OK...
Good!
It's just a recognizance form.
It's still proof of identity.
Stop toying with us, Miss Hong.
I should get my ID card soon.
When you get your official ID card,
you can look us up.
But I really want this suitcase.
I also want my own credit card.
Can you help me register for it now
and I'll submit the ID later?
We'll wait for you.
Sir, would you like to apply for
a virtual credit card?
After the whole morning,
We only have a dozen applications.
He wants a few hundred thousand?
We won't get much from selling this data.
What are you doing?
They needed the information
to borrow from loan sharks.
Why don't we do it ourselves?
(Loan application)
(Loan amount : $400,000)
Are you crazy? $400K?
I thought only small amounts
will be approved
without checking and meeting
the applicant.
You must take a chance.
What's the point of breaking the law?
Brother Kin would have been more vicious.
He's vicious if we screwed up.
Are you scared now?
Just pass everything to Brother Kin
and let him decide.
He just summoned us.
We made money on the bank job.
The Boss saw how hard you worked.
Here's your bonus...
Thanks, Brother Kin...
Yeah! You're so brilliant!
Who's more brilliant? Me or him?
Get lost! Stop taking advantage of her.
Suet, never mind this scumbag.
Speak for yourself...
Shut up, you two.
Order some shooters for us.
Right!
Suet, what would you like?
I'll let you decide.
Let me decide?
Let's go...
OK...
I didn't forget about you.
This is your share.
How come I get a bigger stack
then Dummy and Shek?
Thanks, Brother Kin!
Will they be unhappy about this?
Don't be silly! They're happy to see you.
You've been a big help.
My turn...
Drink up...
OK!
Brother Kin is next...ten...
That's awesome...
That's cheating...
Drain the glass...
I will...
Hurry up...
Open the door!
What's taking so long? Drink...
OK...I'll let you go first...
Miss, are you OK?
I feel dizzy.
Let me help you over there.
You have any chronic illnesses
or on any medication?
I'm a nurse. Anything I can help you with?
I'm fine.
My hospital is nearby.
Let me take you there for a checkup.
Other than feeling dizzy,
you feel anything else?
I don't know.
Did you eat or drink anything?
I was drinking last night.
You have any drug allergies?
I guess not...I don't know.
Cathy!
How is she?
She said she might have had
too much to drink last night.
She doesn't know anything else.
Your BP is very low.
Have you eaten this morning?
When was your last period?
I think...I don't remember.
Is it possible you're pregnant?
A baby! Of course not!
I'm on the pill. I don't have a baby.
Miss, you can't leave yet.
I said I'm fine. I just had too much
to drink.
But your BP is very low.
Your SBP is 90 and DBP is only 55.
You should stay and see a doctor.
Don't be such a pain.
It's my duty to remind you.
Wait...
I don't have money on me.
Can you loan me some money?
Nurse Tse? I'll pay you back later.
I have money to loan you.
But I really think you need
a thorough checkup...
Look!
Is it new?
I personally tested it when I came to work.
The response of the control is quick,
very steady when you go up and down hill.
I already have one.
But this one is electric.
It's so much more convenient.
I think you should try
going outside for some sun.
I can't even leave the hospital,
let alone go outside for some sun.
I recently read an article
about someone with GBS,
Guillain-Barre Syndrome like you,
after a few years' treatment,
had a full recovery.
But this person worked very hard in rehab.
I think if you tried harder,
maybe someday, you can recover too
and leave this hospital
without the use of a wheelchair.
You sounded like I was lazy.
I have done all sorts of treatment.
You should know since you took care of me.
I know you've been good.
That's why I think it's so unfair.
I just saw this girl today,
she's young and running around,
but got so drunk in broad daylight
she had no clue what she was doing.
She was wasting her life away.
And you...who was so happy
with a family and a career
but plagued with this illness.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Ben hasn't been here in four days.
Has it been that long?
I always mark it down. I can't be wrong.
Maybe he's busy. Just call him.
Better not bother him.
I have nothing to do,
so I'm counting the days.
He's so busy, he doesn't have to be here.
But you...if you have time,
please keep me company
so I won't be so bored.
OK!
I can spend time with Mary on Tuesday.
Cathy, next Tuesday is your day off.
Can you take Nurse Chow's shift?
She said something came up at home
and she must take the day off.
But I can't find a substitute.
I can.
Thank you.
Nurse Tse!
Mr. Lau, you finally showed up.
Your wife said you haven't been here
for a few days.
She really missed you.
Has Mary been able to sleep?
Does she still have insomnia?
The doctor prescribed something
to calm her nerves.
She was able to sleep better.
Don't worry, it's quite mild
and won't have side effects.
Thank you. Thanks for looking after her.
Hurry inside. She's waiting.
Thank you.
Did I wake you?
Honey!
Get some sleep. I'll just sit with you.
I can sleep any time I want.
I don't get to see enough of you.
Sorry, I've been busy at work.
But I have nothing to do tonight.
I can stay as long as I like.
The creamy almond tea with egg white
smells really good.
I knew you liked it last time.
But it's not near your office.
You shouldn't go out of your way to get it.
It's on my way today.
Get some rest.
Drive carefully.
I've been busy at work.
I'll come again in a few days.
It's OK. Focus on work. Don't worry about me
Get some rest.
Honey?
Nurse Tse takes really good care of me.
Especially when you're not around.
She spends her personal time with me.
If possible, please thank her for me.
I will. Bye!
It smells great!
You bet! You bought me this jasmine perfume.
I know you like the smell of jasmine.
Let's take a spin in the car
and get out of the city.
Good! It's not every day we have
the day off together.
Exactly! We're both busy.
We hardly have time together.
Even we meet in the hospital,
we must pretend we don't know each other.
Come on...we knew this would happen, right?
It's getting dark. I think it will rain.
It's OK. We should still go.
Let's eat something good.
We can go anywhere.
But I asked a volunteer worker
to take Mary out in the sun.
I guess it won't happen now.
Mary told me you took good care of her.
She wanted me to thank you.
Cathy, how can I thank you?
I'm a nurse. It's my job to look
after my patients.
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm just worried Mary would
eventually find out about us.
She must be angry and heartbroken.
I'm afraid she won't let me
look after her again.
The things I said to encourage her
would go to waste.
You always think of others before yourself.
I should be the one to feel guilty.
Anway, today belongs to us.
Think of nothing else today.
Let's enjoy ourselves for the day, OK?
Shek? Why are you calling me?
Just tell your Boss to contact me.
No more games.
Ben? Who was it?
Nobody. Another phishing call.
Don't lie to me.
You're holding out on me.
You've been very secretive lately.
I can seldom get ahold of you
and you hardly visit Mary at the hospital.
I told you I'm busy at the bank.
What about the money in your account?
Sorry, I didn't mean to check on you.
But...
You're holding out on me too.
You hid the obstetrics check-up
report from me.
Are you pregnant?
I didn't mean to hide it from you...
I'll be a father...
No!
We agreed we won't have a baby.
I don't want to come between
you and Mary.
It's not your fault.
Even if it was an accident,
you can't possibly have an abortion.
At least that's my responsibility.
I don't want to add on to our burden.
You're already in debt because
of Mary's medical expenses.
That's why I need to make
a lot of money ASAP.
I want us to have a proper family.
Let's think this through carefully.
It's not just between us.
She's bound to find out.
It would be devastating to her.
Anyway, we must find a way to
continue to look after her
and give her enough money.
Keep her well-protected
so she won't worry about money again.
You talk about making a lot of money. How?
Are you doing something illegal?
No. Don't worry, I won't be reckless.
Nothing must happen to you...
It'll be OK.
I'm just exploiting loopholes in the law.
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
This is a big deal.
Brother Kin, I want to know
this banker guy is always here.
What does he want?
He's always complaining.
Sounds like he's not happy with the cut.
Would he screw us up?
Rats!
Let's see who'd dare to piss off
Brother Kin.
We'd get even with him.
Yes, we have money now.
We'll go get grasshoppers
and cover his head with them.
You should hold him down
and cut open the top of his skull,
pour in mercury and then grasshoppers...
That sounds familiar...
It's itchy, right?
That sounds like fun.
Anything else more brutal?
More brutal?
Tie him up and leave him in the boonies
where there are loads of ants, insects,
snakes, wild boars...
plaster honey all over him
and let the insects feed on him.
When wild boars spot him...
Shut up! Enough of your nonsense.
He's a good citizen, unlike you two losers.
We're just kidding.
We're shooting the breeze.
People like him are easy to manage.
You can bluff him.
He's begging me to help him make some money.
He wouldn't dare play games.
Exactly! Don't worry about him.
Brother Kin is the boss.
We'll keep him on a leash and
the money will roll in.
You don't know anything.
Don't shoot off your mouth like those two.
I'm sorry.
I intend to treat you to a trip.
Really? I've never been on a plane before!
Me too.
You're in charge of planning this trip.
She'll decide what to do.
I'll check the flights right now.
Bravo, Boss...
Bravo, Brother Kin...
Bravo, Boss!
(A few days later)
It's been a week.
Ben hasn't been here for a week.
Maybe he'll come today.
It doesn't really matter.
I sent him a lot of messages,
but he didn't even read them.
Hello, we're with the CCB,
Commercial Crime Bureau.
Are you Mrs. Lau?
Yes, I am.
Your husband Lau Yue-bun,
is suspected of laundering money
for an underground casino.
We need you to facilitate our investigation.
Because of privacy reason,
we'd like you to step out for a minute.
Wait!
Nurse Tse is a good friend of mine.
I'd like her to stay. Is that OK?
When was the last time you saw your husband?
A week ago. Where is he now?
We have been trying to contact him
but to no avail so far.
You mean he's missing?
He didn't go to work?
That's not possible.
Mary, calm down. Take a deep breath.
Mrs. Lau, are you OK?
Can you continue?
Mrs. Lau, can you tell us
who has been in contact with
your husband lately?
I have been hospitalized for a long time.
We have not been living the life
of an ordinary married couple.
He wouldn't tell me his problems.
I don't know what happened to him.
I really don't know.
But I believe Mr. Lau is a good man.
He would not do anything illegal.
We have reasons to believe
your husband has absconded.
If you hear from him,
please contact us right away.
If you find him...
Of course. We will let you know.
But you're in a hospital,
is it OK for you to take a call?
Or you can contact me.
You want the nurse to be your
emergency contact?
Ben and I have no family in Hong Kong.
Nurse Tse is a trusted friend.
Suet, why did you bring so much stuff?
I don't know how long we'll be gone.
Or where I can buy my things.
Hurry up! There's heavy traffic
going to the airport.
Sorry, Brother Kin.
Suet, carry your own suitcase.
Would Ben be here?
Nurse Tse?!
You're the girl from last time.
Yes, I borrowed $50 from you.
Let me pay you back.
That's OK.
Suet, it's time.
Go on ahead. I'll catch up.
No, come on.
Just go ahead.
Don't worry about the money.
You can pay me later.
Can you...
Suet, what's holding you up?
We have a plane to catch! Bye!
Hurry...
It's been a week. Where are you?
The Police came to see Mary.
Is it about what you told me before?
I looked for you but couldn't find you.
Don't worry. I didn't say anything.
Text me, OK? I'm so worried about you.
I love you.
(Two weeks later)
If you wanted that suitcase,
you should have told me.
I'll buy it for you.
Don't fall for bargains.
Good thing you didn't apply for it.
OK, I'll tell you next time.
But those two have gone too far.
When I saw online the victims of the scam
mentioned applying for a virtual credit card
I knew those two were involved.
Let's go expose them now.
Which one?
I saw them moving something right here.
But I wasn't sure which unit they came from.
What's that stench?
Smells like rotten meat.
Hello?
Is this Miss Tse Chi-kwan?
Speaking.
This is the New Territories East
Crime Unit.
You have news about Ben?
Yes, we found Mr. Lau Yue-bun.
Unfortunately, he is dead.
What?
A few days ago, a couple went to
the 9/F of Po Fat Industrial Building.
The guy is a reporter.
He was looking into a scam that involved
promoting a fake credit card.
They smelled a stench when they
walked past one of the units.
They knocked on the door but
no one answered.
The Police arrived at the scene
and broke the door down
to discover the air con was
turned on full blast,
the air was filled with the smell of
mothballs, air freshener and Chinese herbs.
In the middle of the unit,
we found a wooden crate about
half a person's height.
We pried the crate open
and found a stone coffin inside.
The Fire Services tried to open it
but the cement was too hard.
It took them a long time to open it
and we found the body of a man inside.
The body has decomposed.
We checked the DNA
and confirmed it was Mr. Lau Yue-bun.
The initial autopsy report indicated
the estimated time of death
was two to three weeks ago.
We found multiple injuries on the body
from a fight.
The cause of death was a fatal blow
to the hindbrain by a nail.
Ben...how is this possible? Ben...
Mary...
Ben...
You can identify the body through
the screen behind you.
I must warn you, be prepared...
the decomposition of the body
made him beyond recognition.
Mrs. Lau, do these belong to your husband?
Ben...how could you leave me?
How could you leave me like this?
Mary, I know you're heartbroken,
but you must mind your health.
Ben is gone, I don't want to be alone here.
I don't want to be alone here.
No, you're not alone.
You still have me.
Don't worry, I'll take care of you for Ben.
Miss Tse, when was the last time
you saw Mr. Lau Yue-bun?
About three weeks ago
when Mr. Lau visited his wife.
We chatted about Mary's condition.
You seem quite close to them.
Mary has been staying at Ming Sum Hospital
for three years.
Mr. Lau visited her often.
Naturally, we got acquainted.
The last Tuesday of last month at 3:30pm
what were you doing?
I don't remember.
I need to check my schedule.
I might be at work.
No need. The CCTV nearby
saw you near Po Fat Industrial Building.
What were you doing there?
I went looking for Mr. Lau.
After officers from the CCB
dropped by earlier,
I remembered for some time,
Mr. Lau always bought dessert
for Mary from Sweetness.
Sweetness has no other branches.
The only shop is near
Po Fat Industrial Building.
That place is not near where
Mr. Lau worked or lived.
He must have a reason for going there.
I decided to try my luck
and see if I would run into him.
You seem know Mr. Lau very well
and are aware of his whereabouts.
You claim to be friends with Mrs. Lau.
Are you so close you'd help her
look for her husband?
When you identified the body,
I heard you tell Mrs. Lau,
you'd take care of her for Ben.
What makes you feel you have
such an obligation?
For Ben or for Mary?
They're the same to me.
They are equally close?
Let me ask you this...
Do you know why Mr. Lau is suddenly
involved in the underground casino
and might be helping someone launder money?
I only know Ben is not a greedy man.
Mary's illness has been a heavy
financial burden for him.
Besides...
Miss Tse, level with us.
What's your relationship with Lau Yue-bun?
Ben and I have been together for two years.
We started a year after
Mary was hospitalized.
Come on, 1...2...3...
Careful!
I'm so useless...
Don't say that...
Sir, are you OK?
I can't take this anymore.
I know. Many patients with
rare diseases are like that.
Just follow the doctor's orders.
There's a way.
Cathy!
I've been thinking, let's just break up.
Mary is so nice I don't want to hurt her.
But I don't want to lose you.
During the two years you were together,
you've been taking care of Mrs. Lau.
You really don't mind?
You never asked Mr. Lau to divorce his wife?
No. Ben never wanted to.
They have a good relationship.
Mrs. Lau never knew about your affair?
We didn't want to hurt her
or let this affect her health.
We kept it from her. She didn't know.
When Ben said he was exploiting
loopholes in the law,
I believed him.
Only after he disappeared,
I realized there was more to it.
I wanna know...
If I told you sooner, would he have died?
At least we'll try hard to catch the killer.
That's all I know.
If I think of anything else,
I'll be in touch.
The CCB busted the underground casino
and confiscated the dirty money.
But we're still tracking down the $1.8M
Lau Yue-bun received for money laundering.
You talk about making a lot of money. How?
Are you doing something illegal?
We didn't find his phone at the scene.
We checked with the telecom company
but found nothing from his phone log.
Do you know what happened to the money?
No. I have no idea.
Miss Tse, what you told us just now,
we'll keep it confidential
and won't tell Mrs. Lau.
Thank you, Gogo Sir.
According to the CCB,
a gang of criminals lead by Tai Yat-kin
was helping a local illegal gambling
syndicate with money laundering.
Lau Yue-bun used his authority in the bank
falsified records and opened
a dozen fake accounts
and helped them launder money.
What about these four?
Tai Yat-kin, Cheung Sai-chor,
Hung Wai-shek and Ho Pui-suet?
Any sign of them?
We checked the CCTV at Po Fat
Industrial Building.
Before and after the incident,
they have all been coming in and out
of the building,
with Cheung Sai-chor and Hung Wai-shek
made the most trips.
We also found out they bought
plane tickets in advance.
They must be on the run.
I'm 80% sure they did it.
They bought plane tickets in advance,
that means it was premeditated.
I bet they argued over divvying up the loot
and they killed him on the spot.
They're vicious, but stupid.
The stone coffin is too heavy to move.
It'll be discovered eventually.
What a shame they got away.
What about the wife and the lover?
Anything from them?
The wife looks clean.
But the mistress is a bit fishy.
In what way?
Just think, a decent girl willingly
became the mistress
and took such good care of the wife.
How is that possible?
What do you suspect?
The guy used the mistress to
look after the wife,
or the mistress used the wife
to keep the guy,
or the wife is...
Hey...you're overthinking.
Any kinky relationship is possible
in this world.
A love triangle is relatively
simple already.
The guy needs consolation,
the wife needs care
and the mistress needs love.
To each his own.
If there's mutual consent,
even a love octagon is OK, right?
Oh, samosa!
What kind of relationship is that?
They have samosa for afternoon tea today.
You can still get it if you go down now.
What do you want? Text me.
Thanks, Brother Bo...
Get some rest. I'll fetch your meds.
How do you want Ben's funeral?
I'll do it the way you want.
What flowers should we use
in the mourning hall?
I'll let you decide.
I think you'll pick jasmine.
Why?
Actually, I knew about you and Ben.
Honey, this is for you.
Why jasmine?
I don't know. I like the smell lately.
It smells good. What is it?
You can smell it? It's jasmine.
I'm into jasmine lately.
Last night, I saw a movie called
Next Decision to Leave. It's quite good.
What did you do yesterday on your day off?
Me? I saw a movie,
called Next Decision to Leave. It's good.
Maybe I was too sensitive.
But I'm not surprised at all.
I'm sorry, Mary! I'm so sorry...
I'm telling you not because I blame you.
Now that Ben is gone,
there's no need to hide it.
You must hate me, right?
No woman would want her husband
to be with another woman.
I was heartbroken.
But I'm not angry with you two.
For two years, I saw how Ben changed
from a living corpse to someone
who can smile again.
If you weren't there for him,
I'm sure he couldn't take it anymore.
Ben was a good man and deserved to be happy.
If he was alive,
you two could have been very happy.
No, we want what's best for you.
I'm so sorry. It was my fault.
I failed to control my feelings.
Luckily you failed.
Ben was at least happy towards
the end of his life.
Look at me...there was nothing I could do.
I couldn't take care of him
or make him happy.
I thought about killing myself.
Because I saw how happy Ben was
thanks to you
I didn't feel so hopeless.
You saved him and you saved me too.
No, we only want you to be happy.
I'm so sorry...
Please let me look after you.
Don't try to console me.
You must feel awful over Ben's death.
You must be tired from hiding the truth.
It must have been tough, right?
You can let it out now. Go ahead and cry.
I'm so sorry...
Cathy, your shift ended. You're still here?
I'm filling in for Linda.
But you just came off the graveyard shift.
Can you manage?
I'm OK.
OK, I'm leaving.
Bye!
Almost forgot my phone. Bye!
For two years, I saw how Ben changed
from a living corpse to someone
who can smile again.
If you weren't there for him,
I'm sure he couldn't take it anymore.
Ben was a good man and deserved to be happy.
If he was alive,
you two could have been very happy.
Suet, can you stop pushing the button?
Don't stand over there.
Push where?
It's infra-red, genius! Move!
Quiet! You're getting on my nerves.
God knows how long we're stuck here.
I'm going crazy! Out of my way!
Suet, where are you going?
Where are you off to at this hour?
Brother Kin...
Don't call him. I'm very hungry.
Hungry? You just finished eating.
Cup noodles can't fill me up.
I'm sick of cup noodles for every meal.
We spent all our money.
What else can we eat?
Who knew we'd be stuck in here for so long?
I'm going to run out for a minute.
Come on, I'll get you something, OK?
I don't know...what do you think?
OK...but don't spend all your money.
We don't have much left.
OK, I know.
Come in!
Ching Sir, we got something.
What?
Just got word, a Hong Kong girl in her 20s
showed up at the Wanchai precinct
and claimed she was Suet from
the stone coffin case.
Of her own free will?
Yes. She came to turn herself in.